If anyone kills you,
it will be either the Demon King…
or a human mage.
You're there like the wind
Closing your eyes at sunset
I wonder what's on your mind
With your eyelids open
Your eyes shone like glass
It faintly smelled like a sunny day
Clear up the sky, let flowers bloom
Bloom and blame it on the sunny sky
Even the rain, when it stops
Will make you shine in the sunlight
Calm the stirring sounds in my heart
We go like the sunny wind
Go on and fly over that cloud
Further and further away
It blocked it.
We expected this much.
From here on out,
it's a battle of attrition.
They really are here.
Methode's observations were correct.
Try not to hold me back.
I could say the same thing.
Methode has determined the
exact locations of the enemy.
We can't beat them in a
disorganized free-for-all.
So we'll split up and stop the replicas
before they gather here.
We told each other our weakest matchups.
Your own weakest matchup
is your replica's as well.
Our advantage is that we can
communicate and work together.
As long as we choose the right opponents,
we'll have the upper hand.
Use numbers to deal with anyone
we can't fight alone.
It's funny how easy this is.
If we do this, we can stop the replicas.
Follow the plan.
Got it. Good luck.
There's one concern.
I'm detecting fewer replicas than test-takers.
In particular, I can't find
Ms. Sense's replica, the greatest threat.
You're right. I don't detect it either.
We mustn't overlook Sense's replica.
If she comes at us from behind,
I won't be able to protect Fern.
Worst case, we could both die.
I haven't found Ms. Fern or
Mr. Denken's replicas either.
We'll have to search for them using
more precise close-range detection.
We wouldn't have had to worry
about this if you weren't here.
First-class mages must be able
to overcome unfair adversity.
And this doesn't even qualify as adversity.
Besides, you can pass the test by simply
watching your fellow test-takers' backs.
Is this not a truly kind and peaceful test?
It's down,
but I can't say I enjoyed that.
An ambush.
Damned monstrosity.
I don't recall neglecting
my mana detection.
Lawine, you should break your bottle, too.
You're old enough to know when to quit.
The test will be held again in three years.
Damn it.
I didn't make it in time.
But my help wouldn't
have changed the outcome.
Even with its back turned,
I still don't detect any openings.
Either way, I must at least buy some time.
You're Denken the Imperial Mage, right?
What's going on here?
Are you planning to fight that thing?
I don't think you can beat it.
I know.
Denken, do we have to do this
to conquer the dungeon?
Frieren is currently—
I didn't ask for an explanation.
Is this necessary?
Yes.
Then I'll defeat it.
What are you talking about?
Denken is the strongest one here.
You couldn't even beat Wirbel.
Yeah, that's not how this works.
It's true that I'm an inexperienced
third-class mage.
I'm far weaker than Denken or Wirbel.
But I think I can beat Sense.
This is my specialty.
Reelseiden, a spell that
cuts almost anything.
It cuts anything I think it can,
and it can't cut anything I think it can't.
So what? That spell is easily
blocked by defensive magic.
Oh, right. You watched my battle
against Wirbel, didn't you, four-eyes?
Yeah, defensive magic is for blocking spells.
It's hard for me to imagine cutting it.
I see. Then either way,
it won't work against Sense.
Based only on what we can observe,
that hair has multiple layers of spells
equal to defensive magic cast on it.
I told you, that sort of logic doesn't matter.
I'm talking about what I can visualize.
Hey, wait.
Huh.
Figures. Sorganeil doesn't work.
Well, a person's hair is part of their body.
It's impossible to see all of her at once.
Reelseiden.
As I thought, Übel is fighting my replica.
I already know who will win.
It won't even be a real fight.
It happened two years ago,
during the second-class mage exam.
Burg, a first-class mage,
proctored the second test.
He was so skilled in defensive magic
that he hadn't been injured once
since becoming a first-class mage.
“Immovable Cloak.”
The cloak he created using mana
was imbued with so many defensive spells
that no magical attack could penetrate it.
For the second test, the test-takers fired
offensive magic against Burg and his cloak.
It was a simple test. If they could make him
take just one step back, they passed.
Killing would result in disqualification,
and limits were imposed on offensive
magic to protect the other test-takers.
Next.
No one was worried about Burg.
Oh, I cut too deep.
But he was easily killed
by a no-name girl who'd just recently
become a third-class mage.
This means I fail, right?
I get it. Can I leave now?
I have just one question for you.
Go ahead.
How did you defeat his Immovable Cloak?
Have you ever sewn before, Sense?
No. Why do you ask?
You do seem like you come
from a rich family.
Or do you use magic to handle all that stuff?
I've actually never tried it myself,
since I'm so clumsy.
But I used to watch my sister
sew all the time.
When you cut cloth, you place the scissors
against it like this and slide them through.
It makes a really nice sound.
I liked that sound.
I don't see where you're going with this.
I'm talking about visual imagination.
Cloth can be cut.
You expect to be able to cut it.
She's out of her mind.
It's true that anyone can
imagine cutting cloth.
Even an idiot can do that.
But the world of magic isn't so simple.
Magic can't create anything
the caster can't visualize perfectly,
just as a diminutive ant can't imagine
crushing a colossal dragon underfoot.
Hardly any mages can imagine
penetrating that cloak
and its impregnable magical defenses.
Any mage can tell at a glance that
that cloak blocks all magical attacks.
Truly, any idiot can see that.
As long as people are intelligent organisms,
we cannot escape those fetters.
But she trusted her own intuition instead.
Despite understanding intellectually
that it couldn't be cut,
she constructed a vision of cutting
through the cloak according to her intuition.
Her mind must not function like a person's.
It's practically a superpower.
Can I go now?
Yes.
By the way, Sense, that's some pretty hair.
It must be tough to maintain.
Perhaps I had already lost to her then.
I can't imagine beating Übel.
She's that bad a matchup for me.
You all think too hard.
Hair is something to be cut.
Maintaining my hair?
It's hell.
I don't even want to think about it.
Then you should cut it.
I've got the picture.
So you're buying time until
Frieren defeats the Spiegel.
Yes, that's right.
We defeated three of the replicas.
That will make things easier.
In that case… Oh, my.
Ms. Sense's replica was just destroyed.
This mana…
It was the third-class mage Übel
who defeated it.
That's surprising.
Is it? She was a pretty bad matchup for it.
Battles between mages
are like rock-paper-scissors.
However, it is a complex and difficult game
of rock-paper-scissors with infinite options.
And you want as many options as possible, huh?
Sure. We'll help you slow down the replicas.
I don't make a habit of trusting others,
but I'm not dumb enough to let a winning
horse go when it's right in front of me.
Currently, there are two
dangerous replicas we must stop.
I've determined the location of
one of them: Mr. Denken's replica.
I'd like you to handle that one.
Allow me to handle the other:
Ms. Fern's replica.
She's particularly skilled
at concealing her mana.
Unless we find her replica,
it could ambush and kill someone.
Can you really handle it alone?
Working alone will allow me to
focus better on mana detection.
She's pretty strong, you know.
I have many talents.
When it comes to simply stopping
someone, I'm quite skilled.
Besides, I confirmed with the actual Ms. Fern
that my binding magic would work on her.
Take this.
I can't move.
All right. Let's go fight this thing.
Übel, I'm not imagining this, am I?
Probably not.
After all, you can't move, can you?
My replica is back in action.
Will this keep going until
that Spiegel thing is defeated?
It's a battle of attrition.
This is getting fun.
I couldn't agree more.
Isn't it time for us to get out of here?
This opening won't do either.
Fern wouldn't notice it.
I'll have to do it after all.
The vulnerability in my mana detection
isn't enough to kill me.
You're right.
We could win with a bigger opening, though.
You can win, right?
Then I'll create an opening.
Is that possible?
If I show an opening, then the replica
will show an even greater one.
But that would mean you…
If I focus on defense, it won't be fatal.
Then what strategy should we use?
It's up to you. If you think
we can win, then we can.
How can you be so sure?
Because I underestimate you.
I'm glad to hear that.
That means we have a decent shot at winning.
It's still standing, but that's a fatal wound.
I should finish it—
What happened? Was I attacked?
I don't sense any mana.
I'm not recognizing this attack as a spell.
Incredible, Ms. Frieren.
So this is the height of magic.
But this isn't like you.
You've left yourself wide open.
Well done, Fern.
It's been about eighty years
since I was last forced to use that.
Now, let's end this.
So it's over.
I can't move another millimeter.
Wirbel, carry me.
You guys just can't stay on your feet, huh?
So this is the bottom of the
Ruins of the King's Tomb.
You've conquered the
Such a notable achievement makes you
worthy of becoming first-class mages.
As promised, everyone who made it here
has passed the second test.
So, where are the ladies of the hour?
It's dark and scary in here!
It's dark! It's scary!
I guess I understand that feeling.
Dark! Scary!
The second test is now over.
It can even use healing magic.
Impressive, right?
Uh, yeah.
Who are you?
And I'm alright
Yeah, I hear you
The wind teases this hair that's longer now
There's meaning in everything
Even the days that came to a halt
Now that I finally understand,
I've caught up to you
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
I won't ask to see you, so at least
Let me remember the past, just for today
So, if we were to meet again
No more hesitations, I'd choose the present
Anytime, anywhere, yah
Anytime, anywhere
I'll be there (close your eyes,
and I'll always be there)
Even if there are no absolutes
I'm always aware of your thoughts
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
It's been with me ever since I was little.
You were unlucky this time.
That's the spell Flamme taught you.
I may seem fine, but I'm actually
in a terrible mood right now.
You're in really rough shape.
The third test will now begin.
Fern, let's head back.
Just make fun of me like you always do.
The era of humans has arrived.